Lesson 27. Nothing to sell. And nothing to buy. It has been said that everyone lives by selling
第27课。没什么可卖的。没什么可买的。有人说每个人都通过出售生活
something. In the light of this statement, teachers live by selling knowledge. Philosophers by
某物。鉴于这一说法，教师通过销售知识生活。哲学家
wisdom: n.   智慧, priest: n.   牧师, spiritual: adj. 精神上的
selling wisdom and priests by selling spiritual comfort. Though it may be possible to measure the
通过出售精神上的舒适来出售智慧和祭司。虽然可以测量
value of material good in terms of money. It is extremely difficult to estimate the true value of
物料的价值在金钱方面有益。估计的真实价值非常困难
the services which people perform for us. There are times when we would willingly give everything
人们为我们提供的服务。有时我们会愿意给一切
grudge: v.   不愿给，舍不得给
we possess to save our lives. Yet we might grudge paying a surge in a high fee for offering
我们拥有挽救生命。但是，我们可能会gludge亵付出的高额费用
us precisely this service. The conditions of society are such that skills have to be paid for
我们正是这项服务。社会的条件使得必须为技能支付
in the same way that goods are. Paid for at a shop. Everyone has something to sell. Tramps seem
以商品的方式。在商店付款。每个人都有东西要出售。流浪汉看起来
to be the only exception to this general rule. Beggars almost sell themselves as human being to
成为此一般规则的唯一例外。乞g几乎将自己卖给人类
arouse the pity of passers-by. But real tramps are not beggars. They have nothing to sell and require
引起了路人的遗憾。但是真正的流浪汉不是乞g。他们没有什么可卖的，需要
dignity: n.   尊严
nothing from others. In seeking independence, they do not sacrifice their human dignity. A tramp may
没有别人。在寻求独立时，他们不会牺牲自己的尊严。流浪汉可能
deliberately: adv. 故意地
ask you for money. But he will never ask you to feel sorry for him. He has deliberately chosen to
要你钱。但是他永远不会要求你为他感到难过。他故意选择
consequence: n.   后果，结果
lead the life he leads and is fully aware of the consequences. He may never be sure where the
过着他过着的生活，并充分意识到后果。他可能永远不确定在哪里
afflict: v.   使苦恼，折磨
next meal is coming from. But his is free from the thousands of anxieties which afflict other people.
下一顿饭来自。但是他摆脱了成千上万的焦虑，这些焦虑却困扰着其他人。
ease: n.   容易
His few material possessions make it possible for him to move from place to place with ease.
他的少数物质财产使他有可能轻松地到达地方。
nature: n.   大自然
By having to sleep in the open, he gets far closer to the world of nature than most of us ever do.
通过必须公开睡觉，他比我们大多数人都更接近自然界。
He may hunt, beg, or stead occasionally to keep himself alive. He may even, in times of real need,
他可能会偶尔狩猎，乞求或加油以保持自己的生命。他甚至可能在真正需要的时候
do a little work, but he will never sacrifice his freedom. We often speak of my even, in times of
做一点工作，但他永远不会牺牲自己的自由。我们经常谈论我的偶数
real need, do a little work, but he will never sacrifice his freedom. We often speak of tramps with
真正的需要，做一些工作，但他永远不会牺牲自己的自由。我们经常谈论流浪汉
contempt: n.   蔑视的
contempt and put them in the same class as beggars. But how many of us can honestly say that we have
蔑视并将它们与乞eg一起放在同一班上。但是我们当中有多少人可以诚实地说我们有
not felt a little envious of their simple way of? Life and their freedom from care?
对他们简单的方式不感到有些羡慕吗？生活及其免受护理的自由？